comfortskillz.com 2019-12-16

# Policy-Privacy

##  What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you post a comment.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

###  What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

* To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

###  How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

###  Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

###  Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

###  Third party advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements and collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our website, other sites and other forms of media about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about the practices of some of these third party advertising companies and learn which of these companies allow you to opt-out of this type of information collection, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

###  Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

###  Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

###  Your Consent

**Article submission:**  we offer paid guest posting services, if we published your article and didn't pay within 24hrs for the service we would have all your links removed from the article while your article remains live on our website. By submitting your content for publication on [comfortskillz.com](http://comfortskillz.com/) it means you consent to our publishing T&Cs.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on 10/07/2019

##  **Contacting Us**

Do you have any questions regarding our privacy policy? you may contact us using our contract page.
